What's wrong?
There's someone on the roof.
Jules!
Baby, are you sleepwalking?
Listen.
I don't hear anything.
Come on, baby,
it's 3:00 in the morning.
What now?
I don't know, she said she heard something on the roof.
There were footsteps.
Naturally.
Jingle bells too, right?
Mark, stop.
But I heard him.
Can you take care of this,
please?
I gotta be up in three hours.
Come on, Jules,
let's get back into bed.
No more sugar after dinner,
okay?
Too many bad dreams
and not enough sleep.
But mom!
I didn't have a bad dream.
I really heard someone
on the roof!
Shh.
Keep your voice down.
Don't wake up your brother.
Nobody believes me.
Jules, it's probably just
the house settling.
Or an animal.
You know, sometimes a raccoon
or squirrel can get up there.
It was Santa.
I'm positive.
You know who I really think
it was?
Who?
One of Santa's elves.
An elf?
Mhm.
Sometimes Santa sends a scout
a few days before Christmas Eve
to make sure our house meets
all the necessary
safety requirements.
Like what?
Like making sure the roof
is sturdy enough
to hold all the reindeer,
for one thing.
Can't have them crashing
through the ceiling,
running all through the house,
pooping on everything.
What else?
They have to measure the chimney
to make sure it's wide enough
to fit Santa's big fat belly.
Sometimes he splurges
too much during the holidays.
Just like daddy?
Just like daddy.
Can we leave some milk
and cookies out for the elves?
If you go to sleep right now,
I'll go downstairs
and leave them a plate.
Okay?
You forgot to lock
the front door again.
Perhaps you could have
a little concern
for your family's safety?
By the way, your daughter left
a glass of milk and cookies
for Santa's elves
in the kitchen.
Can you make sure to eat them before she gets up for school?
Hello?
Can you take care of that
when you wake up, please?
When I wake up?
I am up, Jen.
I have been up
because you keep talking to me.
I will take care of it.
Thank you, Mr. Grinch.
Santa?
Timmy!
Timmy, wake up!
Santa's downstairs.
Timmy!
He was putting presents
under the tree, I saw him!
Go away!
Juliet, I told you
to stay out of my--
Babe, what are you doing?
Timmy, Juliet, run!
Juliet!
Timmy!
Help me!
No, please!
Somebody fucking help me!
Help me, please!
Oh fuck, help me!
Help me!
Be advised.
Anonymous caller says possible suspect on lower level.
Armed and dangerous.
Oh, fuck.
Dispatch, I got
a decapitated body down here.
Victim appears to be male.
That's a ten-four.
Dispatch,
I'm not alone down here.
What's-- what's the ETA
on the backup?
I'll have the ship
in the air in a minute!
The ship's on fire.
Eros?
Dean,
I need you to get down here now.
Cell three, east wing.
I think we got
a situation.
Over.
Aww!
Well, wipe your ass
and get down here, pronto!
Help.
Help me!
Please!
Please help me!
Oh, he made me do it.
Please just help me!
Help me!
Help me, fucker!
Yes!
More!
Yo, yo!
You guys, you--
you look so good.
I mean, way better than mine.
I was gonna do
the blood thing, too,
but I was just worried
about the clean up.
But...Can I--
can I get a picture?
I'm gonna post this.
Guys, seriously?
You killed it.
This is awesome!
Aww.
Vicky, you used to be so hot.
Now no one's gonna fuck you.
Pretty girl.
Hi.
Good morning.
Morning.
I'm here to pick up my niece.
She's a patient here.
What's her name?
Shaw.
Sienna Shaw.
Uncle Greg!
Never mind.
-Hey!
- How are you?
- Good.
-How are you?
-Good.
-It's good to see you.
-You too.
Wow.
You look good.
-No, I got it.
-No, no, no, I got it.
-I insist.
-Thanks.
Welcome.
So do we run, or...
Gotta sign out first.
So, uh, how's my little
partner in crime?
Oh,
she's not so little anymore.
Uh, she's great.
Man, beautiful.
Sassy as hell
and talented like you.
In fact,
you're all she ever talks about,
so, little warning,
just get ready
to have your hands full,
because she misses you.
I miss her, too.
Hey.
We're home!
All right.
Hello?
Sienna!
Incoming!
Oh, hey!
Hey!
Hey, Gabs.
Oh my god, you got so big!
When did that happen?
Never leave me
for this long ever again.
I won't.
I promise.
Oh, you got glitter
all over your face.
It's just sugar.
We were baking.
Did you want to help?
Gabbie, Sienna's not even
in here two minutes.
Why don't you let her
get settled first, all right?
Fine.
Yeah, I'd love to.
I'm so happy to see you.
Me too.
How was the trip?
Fine.
Wanna see your room?
Go ahead.
We'll catch up later.
Yeah. All right.
I'll see you guys later.
And don't pull her arm out.
- Ready?
- Yes.
Oh my God.
It looks like a fairy tale
exploded in here.
Do you like it?
Me and mommy redecorated,
but I picked out most of it.
I know how much you like
dragons and wizards.
I love it.
Really?
Yes, really.
This is the coolest room ever.
Are you kidding?
I don't know what to say,
this is beautiful.
Made this for you too.
Gabs.
'To Sienna, my big sister
from another mister.
I've missed you more than ever.
And getting into trouble
hasn't been nearly as much fun
without you.
Looking forward
to the best Christmas ever,
filled with fun,
smiles, and laughter.
Love, Gabby.
P.S. We still haven't made it
to the moon.'
To the moon!
Our little cardboard
rocket ship.
You remember?
Of course I do.
Come here.
Jesus.
-Yeah.
-Stinks in here.
A real beaut, ain't she?
Shit!
It's a rat, kid,
not the devil.
Yeah.
Are you alright?
Oh, you've been skittish
all day.
I just hate places like this.
It's like they got a soul
and they're pissed that
-we're tearing 'em apart.
-Oh, shit.
Please don't tell me
you believe all the stories
about this place.
What stories?
Back in the early 90s,
some maniac abducted
and killed over a dozen kids
in this town.
They buried all the bodies
in the basement here
in this building.
Now everyone swears
the place is haunted.
Are you fucking with me?
You're fucking with me.
Of course I'm fucking with you.
Now come on.
I'll take the first floor
and the basement.
You... upstairs.
Skittish all day.
So, what do you think?
More Blaster Man?
What's the matter
with Blaster Man?
I thought you liked him.
You only draw boys.
Boys, boys, boys.
That's not true.
I draw girls all the ti--
that is a girl right there.
Look at that.
That is a girl.
But she's not a superhero.
Last time you said
you were going to draw a girl
that could beat up Blaster Man.
Remember?
You pinky swore!
That's sacred.
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I will tell you what, though.
As soon as I'm finished
with this comic,
I'm gonna make you
something really special.
How's that? Okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, well.
Okay.
Time for bed.
Sisi!
Wait a minute.
I do have something for you.
I woke up back
in the clown café,
encased in glass.
My lungs filled with ice water.
This wasn't a dream
or a hallucination.
Okay, give me that.
This isn't
for public consumption, nosy.
It's my diary. Okay?
It's for my eyes only.
Got it?
Got it.
What's the clown café?
It's a bad place.
A place I don't want
to think about.
Happy thoughts
from now on. Okay?
Okay.
Jingle bells, jingle bells,
this place fucking smells
Disgusting.
What the hell is that?
Anybody home?
What the fuck?
Hello?
It's not real.
It's not real, right?
Hey, Jackson!
Anybody home?
Yoo-hoo.
What the fuck?
Holy shit!
Dennis!
Hey!
Get your ass up here!
Now!
Are you real?
No!
No! No!
I think we need to make
some cookies.
Yeah. For dessert!
We need to-- Yeah!
We're gonna go all out, man.
Chocolate and peanut butter,
you are right.
That's the combination.
You know, those coconut peanut
butter ones are amazing.
This is going to be
a Christmas extravaganza.
I'd like to go see
those lights again.
I wanna see the lights.
I like the holiday market that
they have over there.
Gabs, stop starin'.
It's rude.
What?
I like her scars.
Gabbie!
No, it's fine.
No, it's not.
It's very inappropriate.
I just think they're cool.
You know what?
Why don't you show her
your new scar?
Look at this thing.
Bad boy.
Ooh.
How'd you get that?
Fell off my bike
during summer break.
And landed on a broken bottle.
Oh, yeah.
Seven stitches, too.
There was so much blood,
and like this piece
of fat oozing out.
All right, all right.
Can we change the subject,
please?
I don't wanna think about blood
and fat while we're eating.
So much blood.
Okay, honey.
You're disgusting.
Regardless,
Christmas hasn't really been
the same around here
since someone stopped
believing in Santa Claus.
When did that happen?
When I was, like, eight.
Oh, stop.
You were older than that.
No,
I just went along with it
so you and Daddy
wouldn't feel bad.
I've been finding presents
stashed around the house
for years now.
Yeah, that's 'cause
you're a little snoop.
Yeah.
Finding is a loose term.
More like investigating
and discovering, really.
Can you pass the rice?
It's not my fault that
they're really, really bad
at hiding presents.
Dude, it was under
the floorboard,
under the carpet.
Pass the rice, please?
Oh, she's also notorious
for opening presents
and then re-wrapping them.
Not very well, either.
Sienna!
If you don't pass the rice,
I'm not gonna leave.
Please? Pass the rice?
Sienna?
Hello, Sienna?
You know, I'm dead because
of you, okay?
You led us to him.
You and that little shithead
brother of yours.
I'm dead and you killed me.
Just like you killed
your mother.
That was bad.
I didn't...
But anyway.
I mean,
that's how he always did it.
He's kind of cute.
Sienna?
You all right?
Yeah.
Sienna...
I mean, no amount of medication
is gonna stop me from being here
in front of you.
You killed me.
The least you can do
is pass the rice.
Pass the rice.
Pass the rice!
Excuse me.
Finish eating, sweetie,
so we can have
our fortune cookies.
Whoa!
Okay, wow.
Thanks for knocking, Shaw.
Sorry.
Wait!
Um, aren't you going
to introduce us?
Wow.
Uh, Shaw, this is,
um, Mia.
Hi.
She's a really big fan
of yours.
I'm not a fan, you asshole.
She's obsessed
with the Miles County Clown.
Like all that true crime shit.
She thinks
you're a celebrity, dude.
Don't listen to him.
Like, literally, ever.
Um, hi.
It is so nice to meet you.
Hi.
I seriously know,
like, everything about you.
Everything online at least,
um, I've been following you
for years.
Dude, you're a legend.
You survived Art the Clown,
See? Fucking fangirl.
Eat me.
After you get his autograph.
Um, listen, I actually
had a little bit of a favor
that I wanted to ask you.
You see, my roommate and I,
we have a true crime podcast.
It's called Graven Image.
And our Miles County Massacre
episodes?
They get our biggest hits
by far.
So I was wondering
if maybe you'd be willing
to come on as a guest sometime?
I seriously would be so honored.
I don't really do
things like that.
Jesus, do you really think
he wants to dredge up
the worst experience
of his life?
I mean, the kid's just trying
to move on.
Right, Shaw?
Okay, well, I get that,
but I just--
I think a lot of people would
really like to hear from you
after all this time.
Oh my god.
Come on.
I-- I'll think about it.
He'll think about it.
Great.
Hah.
Shaw, are you coming
to the Beta Christmas bash
tomorrow night?
I gotta take this.
Oh.
Yeah.
Girl callin'
It was great meeting you,
Mia.
You too.
God, my man needs
to get laid so bad.
Hey.
How are you?
I'm, uh, doing good.
Just got out of class.
I just got to Aunt Jess's.
Yeah, a couple hours ago.
It's really good to hear
your voice.
You know, I-- I miss you.
I miss you, too.
Is, uh, everything all right?
I'm calling because, um...
I'm-- I'm really excited
we're going to be spending
Christmas together.
It's been too long.
Yeah, it has.
I'm, uh, really looking
forward to it.
Well, uh,...
...I guess I'll see you
in a couple days?
Love you.
Love you more.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It's, um, just this
new medication I'm on.
It makes me queasy sometimes.
Oh.
I need to be creative.
Wanna be my canvas?
All right.
Something's happening here.
Can I see already?
Hold your horses.
I mean, you are starting
to look quite enchanted,
if I do say so myself.
Like a fantasy princess.
All right.
We're going to put a little bit
more elven eyeshadow
to go with that magic blush.
Close your eyes.
You know,
you could be a professional
makeup artist, right?
Why, thank you.
I actually forgot
how much I enjoy this.
Eyes open.
Great.
All right, let's do some lips.
How'd you get those scars?
You and these scars.
I got into a fight.
Did you win?
Yeah, I won.
Chin up.
All right,
gimme one of these.
You're all done.
You wanna see this mystical
masterpiece?
Yeah.
Wow!
It looks amazing.
Your face did all the work.
Take a picture!
Can I join the mile high club
in your sleigh?
Oh my god!
Oh, ho ho ho.
I'd fuck ya.
No, Mrs. Claus would shank me
in my sleep.
- My wife's dead.
- Okay.
Wanna come down my chimney?
Oh my god,
come in her chimney, come!
I've got a chimney.
Okay, girls.
I'm a naughty little reindeer.
I wanna do drugs
on your stomach!
Be good.
Ho ho ho!
Oh, shit.
God damn!
I think I know
what I want for Christmas.
That Santa outfit comes
with some perks, dude.
Girls!
I don't remember
if I told you, but,
so I've been in entertainment
for a long time.
I'm Santa now, I was Elvis.
Those girls!
Laughlin, 1980s.
Whoo!
Nothing like this.
To Laughlin.
Laughlin!
To Laughlin?
I'm good.
Ow, ow!
You racist piece of shit!
Shit.
Get a load of this fucking guy.
Friend of yours, Eddie?
That is a fucking first.
All right, well,
now hold on now, listen.
I'm wearing the outfit, right?
So it's just like Elvis.
He gets the full Santa
experience if he wants it,
all right?
Hello.
Hi, hi!
You--
Come on over.
It's fine.
Yeah!
Hi, hi.
Yes, yes, yes, that's--
that's me, that's me.
Guilty as charged.
Hey Santa,
it looks like you got a fan.
What's with the outfit, pal?
Yeah, did the circus
come to town?
Hey, buddy.
Watch it.
That's the real deal.
That's my--
that's my beard.
If Santa doesn't have
a real beard,
he's not a real Santa Claus.
Hey, fella,
what's in the bag?
Oh, he's gonna show us.
Hey, what do ya got?
What do ya--
Usually I'm the one
who's bringing
the magical sack of toys.
What?
Oh, that's good!
Okay. That's enough.
All right, now, look,
I'm startin' to like this guy,
I really am. Clowny.
Put--
put your little horn away.
Have a seat.
And, uh,
Santa'll buy him a drink.
Clowny,
I'm startin' to like you.
Here you go.
I hope I gave you
enough marshmallows.
Oh.
It's perfect.
Thank you.
Some peace and quiet
around here, finally, huh?
You must be exhausted.
No, I...
...I feel...
What?
Normal?
Look, I'm not going
to pretend that
I know what you're going
through, because I don't.
I-- I can't even begin
to imagine it.
But I promise it'll get better.
You remind me so much of mom.
Before dad died,
she was the sweetest person.
Could talk to her
about anything.
Yeah, she was.
Mouth like a truck driver,
though.
She cursed so much.
So much!
She once called
Sister Rosemary a C-U-N-T
in the sixth grade.
I don't know
where she came from!
Nobody in our family
talks like that.
I miss her.
I miss her so much.
I know, sweetie.
I know.
I miss her, too.
Hey, Santa.
Looks like you got
some competition.
It's Clowny Claus!
No.
Hey, you're a natural.
You look good.
But don't get it dirty.
And remember to give it back.
You don't want to get
on Santa's naughty list.
Hey, why don't you tell Santa
what you want for Christmas,
little boy?
Better hygiene?
All right, come on,
let's have a drink, uh,
for everybody, okay.
Come on.
Got ID?
He's obviously old enough.
All right.
You think I'm gonna lose
my license for this guy?
Don't bust the clown's balls.
This is normal to you?
Sorry about this, Clowny.
There, see?
He's got it.
Maurice Jackson?
Eddie, you're killing me.
Can we just celebrate?
Come on.
Fuck it.
It's Christmas.
All right,
let's have a drink!
To my new friend, huh?
To Maurice Jackson!
-Maurice Jackson.
-Cheers!
What the fuck
is the matter with you?
What's your problem, pal?
Guy buys you a drink
and you spit it back
in his fucking face?
Hey, man.
That's--
that's wrong.
Now look, you see,
you-- you were just rude,
and you shouldn't have
been rude.
Let's go, Clowny.
Get up.
No, I'm not ki--
Oh, shit.
What the...
What the fuck are you doing?
He peed on him!
Fucking told you!
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm gonna fucking kill you,
you sick fuck!
I'll fucking kill him!
Hey, come on,
you motherfucker!
Fuck you!
Goddammit.
Smokey, get his bag!
Son of a bitch!
This is my busy weekend.
I know.
What the fuck is in this?
Jesus, fuck!
Get that the fuck out of here.
What? What? Hey!
You motherfucker!
I'll fucking kill you!
I got it.
- Goddammit!
- Want me to call the cops?
I don't want you to call
the cops.
I want you to call
a fucking dry cleaner.
- Dry cleaner!
- Smokey, get a fucking mop!
I told you, don't let him
the fuck in here.
You said he's fuckin' normal!
Sit down, sit down!
Fuckin' 'you told me.'
Have a fucking drink.
Can't take a fucking hint,
can you?
I'm not going to tell you again.
Oh, fuck.
Eddie?
And Smokey?
Oh, god, Smokey!
Oh, no, oh, god, oh, god.
No!
Oh, god.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Sir! No, sir.
No, no, no, no, sir.
No, no, please.
Please, please.
Let me be the first to apologize
for whatever's happened
here tonight.
I don't--
I don't know what happened.
Here, take it!
Take it, take it, take it!
It's yours.
You looked really good in it!
Take it all!
You be Santa!
Clowny,
we're in the same business.
It's just me and you, remember?
It's just me and you.
We're in the same business.
We make people happy.
Help me, help me!
God, help me!
Hey, you pay attention to me.
Help me!
That isn't even funny.
It's not funny.
The fuck?
Come on.
Oh, Clowny, please,
please, Clowny, help me!
Please, god!
Oh, god help me!
Oh, god.
Clowny, come on.
You look good, Clowny.
You look good.
Oh, yeah,
that's never looked better.
Look, I'll go now, then.
You know, you're--
you're Santa Claus, right?
So I can go.
Yeah.
Oh, help!
Help me!
Clowny!
What the hell is that?
Oh god, oh god.
Clowny.
Clowny, look at me.
Clowny,
I'm not really Santa Claus.
No, no, wait.
Listen to me.
I have a name.
I have a real--
No, I have a real name!
My-- my name
is Charles Johnson.
Clowny, and I have a wife,
a wife!
I have a wife and two kids.
Hey, Clowny.
No, no, no, Clowny, no!
Listen to me,
Clowny I beg you.
Listen, I have four gorgeous
grandchildren.
And their names, their names
are Brian and Denise and--
Clowny!
Clowny,
it hurts so much, please!
So, how is she?
As good as can be expected.
I think Gabbie brought some
life back into her today, right?
It's nice to see her smile
a little bit.
Oh my god, Gabbie.
She follows Sienna around like
a brand new puppy.
It's concerning.
Now they're going
Christmas shopping tomorrow.
Just the two of 'em?
Mhm.
Sienna wants to pick up
a gift for Jonathan.
You really think
that's a good idea?
They'll be fine.
Jess...
...did you not see
what happened today?
What if that little episode
was just a microcosm
of what's to come?
What if that shit gets worse?
I'm not gonna abandon her.
She's healing.
It's gonna take time.
She's taking her medication.
All I'm saying is, let's keep
our guard up, all right?
That's all I'm saying.
Okay.
Merry Christmas!
What is your name?
This way please. This way.
All right, sweetie,
look over here.
Ready?
Don't go past this point.
You'll be in trouble.
Thank you.
Next.
All right, buddy,
smile for the camera.
You guys ready to meet Santa?
What are you going to ask for?
Makeup?
Yeah.
Are you old enough for makeup?
Okay. Thank you.
Next.
Hey, Gabs.
You think he'll like this?
Hmm.
Not sure.
I don't think Jonathan
is really into black anymore.
Jonathan doesn't wear black?
Mr. Death Metal?
I don't think he listens
to that anymore either.
Just a phase, I guess.
All right, well, then,
what does he wear now?
I don't know.
Normal clothes?
Really narrows it down.
Thanks, Gabs.
Okay, sweetie.
You ready?
Okay.
Thank you.
-Bye, Santa.
-Bye.
At least it's better
than Louisville.
You got a point, Bob.
Let's take a break.
Oh.
Sorry, folks.
Santa's gotta go feed
his reindeer.
You know,
I'm not in charge here.
Can we go on a break too?
Sure.
This one's nice.
Hmm, not bad.
Is it your favorite?
Top three.
All right, well,
then you choose.
You know your dad
better than me.
Hey!
What are you staring at?
Nothing.
Come on, you ready?
Let's get going.
You okay?
Yeah.
Sienna Shaw
is the prime suspect.
Do you want to just do that?
Okay, she's linked
to every single victim?
Okay?
She was at every crime scene?
A history of mental illness
in her family?
with Art the Clown?
And there's no body.
How about you show me
the dead clown's body?
Dude, there's so many holes
in that story.
Like, how do you not see that?
If Jonathan Shaw
hadn't testified
on his sister's behalf,
she'd probably be serving
a life sentence right now.
You shouldn't be saying
that shit.
You look great.
Your, uh, your scars
are healing up nicely.
Yeah, yours too.
Gabbie thinks I look cool,
apparently.
So...
...Why'd you want to see me
right now?
I-- I missed you.
I mean, can't a sister see
her little brother?
Um, actually,
I was, uh,
I was thinking,
why don't you come over
Aunt Jess's tonight?
I mean,
why wait till Christmas Eve?
You've gotta be done
with classes by now, right?
I can't, I can't tonight.
Why not?
There's a party on campus
that I was invited to.
Really?
Oh.
That's good.
No. I'm happy.
Jonathan Shaw spotted in public!
What is this,
a Christmas miracle?
Dick!
Um, Sienna, this is Cole,
my roommate. Cole.
Oh, wow.
Hey, big sis.
I've, uh, heard a lot about you.
It's nice to finally meet you.
Hi.
Well, you've got a cool
baby bro here, and I treat him
like he's my own.
You treat me like shit.
Oh, he jokes.
Oh, shit.
Let me get out of here.
Oh my God.
Sienna!
You're Sienna Shaw!
I, I seriously so--
I can't believe I'm sitting here
with you guys.
I was literally just telling
your little brother.
I'm sorry.
I'm probably being
a little weird.
I'm just super stoked
to see you.
Mia has been following
our story very closely.
I am a true crime enthusiast,
and I've actually been following
your case in particular
for years on my podcast,
and no rush or anything,
but I do know the five year
anniversary is coming up
and the fanbase is rabid.
Like, we would literally
kill for anything.
I'm thinking, Get Readys
with Me, What I Eat in a Day...
Just show us how you're coping.
You know, what you do
on a daily basis,
anything like that.
How I'm coping?
Yeah.
How we're coping?
Well, uh, I've been in and out
of a psychiatric hospital
for the past five years.
Oh.
I see images of my dead friends
and relatives on a daily basis,
images that wake me up screaming
in the middle of the night.
I have hideous scars
all over my body,
and every time I see them,
I think of how that sick fuck
who ruined our lives
is still out there.
And you want to know
how I'm coping with everything?
You guys are all
the same leeches.
Sienna.
Can't you act like a human being
for one fucking second?
Sienna, what's wrong with you?
I saw him today.
Who?
Where?
At the mall, with Gabbie.
How can you be sure
it was really him?
I'm not, I'm not sure
of anything anymore.
I don't know what's real
or what's in my fucking head.
Well,
what'd you see exactly?
He was dressed as Santa Claus.
Santa Claus?
Okay, I know, I know
how that sounds...
...but it was him.
I could--
I could feel it.
We both know this isn't over.
You don't know that.
I mean, Jesus Christ,
you cut his fucking head off.
Come here.
Hey, what is this?
Jonathan!
Hey, why are you
shutting me out?
I'm not shutting you out.
You don't believe me?
Why would he come back here?
Even if he was alive,
which he isn't.
Wouldn't you want to get as far
away from here as possible,
as far away from you?
Maybe it's me they want.
Isn't that what you said?
Boy genius.
What are you,
Mr. Academic now?
You think you're too good
for your own--
I'm sorry.
At least I'm fucking trying.
I'm proud of you.
We need each other, okay?
I need you.
What we need to do
is move on.
Let it go.
It's over.
'We have to destroy
the little girl
before it's too late, Sienna.
Destroy her because
she's inhuman.
A demon.'
I still have your letters.
You wrote me almost every week
when I first went away.
Remember that?
All your theories
about demonology, possession.
You became obsessed.
But you weren't crazy.
You were right!
I'm not listening to this.
You listen to me!
'Sometimes demons
try to enter our world,
only they can't do it alone.
They have to choose a vessel,
someone recently deceased
who functions as a bridge
between worlds.
But not just anyone.
Someone sinister, depraved.
The worst kind of evil.
Like a serial killer?'
'If a demon enters this world
in the flesh,
a counterpart must be
appointed to stop it
from becoming too powerful.
It's you, Sienna.
As long as you're alive,
they're vulnerable,
and they know it.'
That's why Daddy created
the sword.
Whoever chose me
was guiding him.
He was preparing me for this.
It's using Victoria Heyes
as a host now, isn't it?
That's why she disappeared
that night.
What do you wanna do?
What, do we just up
and leave town?
Call the cops, tell Aunt Jess
and Uncle Greg?
No. They'll never believe us.
Especially me.
I have to go back
to the Terrifier.
Why?
It's still buried there,
isn't it?
And if I'm right,
it might be the only thing
that can stop them.
Jingle bells, jingle bells,
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to ride in
a one-horse open sleigh
Jingle bells, jingle bells,
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to ride in
a one-horse open sleigh
Hey, Santa!
Dashing through the snow
On a one-horse open sleigh
O'er the fields we go
Laughing all the way
Bells on bobtails ring,
making spirits bright
What fun it is to ride and
sing a sleighing song tonight
Sarah, get back over here!
Wow.
Thanks, Santa.
Hey, Santa's handing out
presents!
Jingle bells, jingle bells,
Jingle all the way
Santa claus is coming along
Riding down this way
Joy to the world
the Lord is come
Let earth receive her king
What's going on here?
That's not Bill.
What?
That's not our Santa Claus.
And heaven and nature sing
And heaven and Heaven
and nature sing
Kids, clear out of here.
Get goin'!
Joy to the world
the savior reigns
Let men their songs employ
Who is this Santa?
He's scaring my kid.
Yeah, he's scaring me, too.
What do you think you're doing?
You can't be here.
I said, let's go.
Come on.
Get the kids out of here.
Sarah!
What did I say?
Christ almighty,
what's the uproar, people?
Get the fuck out!
Don't come back!
And makes the nations prove
Come on!
No!
The glories
of His righteousness
Corey?
And wonders of His love
Corey,
get back over here!
Back in line, kids.
Time for the real Santa.
I wonder what I got.
Corey!
What's that?
Jesus! You scared me.
What are you doing,
snooping around like that?
Is it for me?
None of your business,
nosy.
It is, isn't it?
No, it's not.
And don't even think about
opening it, all right?
What happened to your hands?
My hands?
I fell, okay?
I slipped on some ice
and took a ridiculously nasty
spill in front of, like,
20 college students.
Is that what you wanna hear?
I wish I saw that.
You think that's funny?
Come here!
No!
Christmas
Shady
Save us all
from satan's power
God rest ye merry gentlemen
Let nothing you dismay
Yo, grab that door?
Here we go.
Thank you.
That is wicked!
Kegs here!
Oh.
Something smells amazing.
You're back late.
How's your brother?
Oh, he's good.
Yeah.
He's going to a campus
Christmas party tonight.
Jonathan's going
to a Christmas party?
Oh!
Nice to hear
he's socializing.
Yeah.
God, these are so freaking cute,
Aunt Jess.
Those are my favorite.
Do you want some?
No, thanks.
Oh, sorry, I forgot you don't
like cereal anymore.
Who doesn't like cereal?
Sienna.
What? Sienna,
you don't like cereal?
I mean, I can understand tofu
or Lima beans,
but cereal's the best.
I know, honey. Chill.
Yeah, I just try to stay away
from too much sugar.
You got more willpower than me.
Hey Gabs, what do you say
we go upstairs
and play some board games?
Let's go.
Yeah.
I think we need some
Christmas tree sprinkles.
You need
What are you in the mood for?
I have a ton.
Pictionary,
Guess Who, Monopoly.
I like Monopoly.
Takes forever, though.
I never told you
I don't like cereal.
What?
How'd you know
I don't like cereal?
Gabbie?
Did you read my journal?
I'm sorry.
Please don't be mad at me.
Where is it?
I put it back in your room.
How much of it did you read?
Tell me.
All of it?
Jesus, Gabbie.
You-- you promised me.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to know
what happened to you.
Is it true?
All that stuff about
the clown and Uncle Michael?
You saw him today,
didn't you?
At the mall.
That's why you freaked out.
Gabbie, I'm sick.
I see things that aren't there.
And sometimes I write about it
in my journal and talk about it
with people who can help me.
So you didn't really chop off
the clown's head
with the magical sword?
No.
Damn,
that would've been so cool.
Gabs.
You have to promise me
you're not gonna tell anyone
what you read
in my journal, okay?
Not your parents,
not your friends at school?
No one.
Promise me.
I promise.
Pinky swear.
Okay.
Let's play Pictionary
so I can kick your ass.
You're probably
still passed out.
Uh, look, I just wanted
to call and see if...
...you're okay, man?
Um...
Yeah.
Gimme a call back whenever
you get this, but, uh,
if you can't reach me,
I'll be at the Beta bash, so...
Peace.
You don't think I was that
insensitive before, do you?
Uh, yes.
Yes, I do actually.
Okay, I get
it's like a touchy subject
and all, but come on,
it didn't happen yesterday.
It happened five years ago.
Yeah, I don't think
that's something
you ever really get over.
Well, she still didn't mean
to snap at me the way she did.
Besides, talking it out
is good therapy.
I was basically doing
her a favor.
Wow, how selfless of you.
Well, what about Jonathan?
Do you think he'd still be
willing to do it?
I don't know, Mia.
Cole,
I want that interview.
I mean, sitting across
from someone
who actually encountered
Art the Clown?
The most famous serial killer
since Jack the Ripper.
It's historic.
'Encountered.'
That's putting it mildly,
wouldn't you say?
The kid was almost butchered.
You know what I mean.
I want to know
what it's like to be
in the presence
of that kind of evil.
What goes through
your brain
when he's close enough to you
that you feel his breath
on your body?
What does he smell like?
When you look into his eyes.
What do you see?
Is there a soul or...
'His eyes!'
You sound like
you want to fuck him.
I don't want to fuck him.
I mean,
you're friendly with Jonathan.
You said he looks
up to you, right?
Maybe you can convince him
for me,
Mia...
Come on.
Do it for me.
Please?
I'll be nice,
I promise.
Mhm.
All I need is 20 minutes,
tops.
I'll make it worth your while.
Oh, wow.
You are very persuasive.
I'll see what I can do.
Okay, so remind me
how to play this again.
It's been a while.
Wait.
We need more players.
Dad, come on.
just outside of Miles County.
Dad?
Again, five people have been
declared dead at this time
and six
are in critical condition.
The explosion happened
around 5pm this afternoon
at the Centerville Mall,
as the children gathered around
the holiday center display.
No suspects are in custody
at this time,
as the investigation
is still underway.
Close?
I was pretty damn close!
Too close for my liking.
Was it a terrorist attack?
I don't know, baby.
There was this guy, and he
was dressed as Santa Claus,
and he was handing out
presents to kids.
Every little kid that was there.
I heard a commotion,
and then I saw security
leading the guy out.
And then, bam!
There was an explosion
right there.
Holy shit.
He's here, he's here.
It's not safe.
Sienna,
what are you talking about?
The Miles County Clown.
I saw-- I saw him today.
Listen to me.
No, I saw him today.
- All right.
- Okay, I saw him.
And I wasn't gonna say
anything
because I knew
you wouldn't believe me.
Okay.
And he's gonna come for us.
-No, honey. No.
-He's gonna come.
All right.
We have to get-- As long as
I'm here, we're in danger.
Okay? We're in danger.
We have to get as far away
from here as possible.
There's no Miles County Clown,
Sienna.
No, it was him, okay?
I saw him.
- Nobody's coming for--
- Listen to me.
Stop it!
You are scaring Gabbie.
Jonathan!
We have to call Jonathan.
I will call Jonathan.
If they know-- Jonathan,
then we have to call Jonathan,
right now.
Hey, Uncle Greg.
Jonathan.
Dude, your sister
is freaking out over here, man.
She saw something on the news,
and she's adamant
about getting you over here
as soon as possible.
She thinks you're in danger.
What'd she see?
She saw the news, man,
about the explosion.
Look, I think a few people
were killed, and now she's--
Look, dude. It's bad.
I need to talk to him, okay?
Sienna!
Jonathan.
Oh! It's happening,
it's happening, okay?
You need to let Uncle Greg
come and get you right now.
You're not safe.
Okay, I'll come over.
Did you get it?
Yeah, I got it.
See you soon.
Okay.
I gave her something
to help her sleep.
Good.
You were right.
We'll talk about it
when I get back.
Be careful.
Call me if anything.
Hey, sweetie.
You okay?
Where's Sienna?
She's sleeping.
She's gonna go back
to the hospital, isn't she?
I don't know, baby.
I don't want her to.
But if she's not well,
we gotta do what's best for her.
What if she's right?
What if the Miles County Clown
is back?
He's not, Gabs.
You're safe.
Sienna's just scared.
Nothing's going to happen
to any of us, okay?
Just get some rest.
Jonathan and Daddy
will be back soon.
Okay.
I love you.
Love you too, mom.
Help!
Help us!
Oh, Mia, no, Mia!
Mia!
No!
Hey, Uncle Greg.
Jonathan.
I'm here.
Where? I don't see you.
I'm parked right
where you told me.
I'm in front of your dorm.
Jonathan,
can you hear me?
Sisi, wait a minute.
I do have something for you.
Ta-da!
You drew it!
I knew you would!
Yeah, I just-- I didn't think
it was really ready,
but, um...
...you like her?
I love her.
She's beautiful.
Is she an angel?
Not just an angel.
She's an angel warrior.
You see that fire sword?
It has special powers.
She can defeat any bad guy
with that sword,
and he can never hurt her.
Wow.
Can she defeat Blaster Man?
Oh, yeah.
Ten Blaster Men.
So cool.
Well,
now you get to name her.
I can name her?
Of course you can.
It's your character,
isn't it?
Thanks, Dad.
You're very welcome,
sweetheart.
Dad?
Daddy?
Go!
Daddy!
Let go.
What's that?
Sisi,
I need you to listen to me.
Look.
Look at me, look at me.
I am always with you.
We have got to put
a stop to this before
it goes too far, Jess.
What do you suggest we do?
I think we should call
the doctor immediately.
That's what we should do.
I'm not doing that.
It's obvious she's unstable.
She's just confused.
Confused my ass.
Come on.
There's no telling
what she's liable to do.
I'm not sending her back
to that place on Christmas Eve.
Listen to me.
She is a danger right now.
Not only to herself,
but to us, to our family.
We have to think about Gabbie.
Shh!
Keep your voice down.
I don't want Sienna to hear us.
Oh, I don't give a fuck
if she hears us or not.
As a matter of fact,
you know what I think
we should do to Sienna?
I think we should go upstairs
and smother her in her sleep.
Then we'd be free.
Free from her bullshit.
Free...
Free, free, free, free, free...
Free!
Crazy lady!
You're a danger to yourself
and everyone else
in this fucking house.
Crazy lady!
Crazy! Crazy!
Gabbie!
Cheese, bitch.
Cheese.
To Mommy.
Love, Gabbie.
Try it on, Mommy.
Aww, it looks good on you,
Mommy.
Hah!
If you scream, I'm gonna rip
your fucking tongue out.
Where's my daughter?
Oh, what did you do
to my daughter?
I thought you'd never ask.
Merry Christmas, Mommy.
Hi, Gabbie!
No!
Hi, Mommy!
We love you.
We miss you.
That's not my daughter.
But it is!
Can't recognize
your own flesh and blood?
I gave you a present,
Mommy.
And now I want you
to give me one.
Fuck you!
No, no!
I love you, Sienna.
Kill them both.
Make them suffer.
You first.
No, no!
Stop!
No!
You're no savior.
I'm gonna take
everything you love.
Then I'm gonna invade that
pretty pink flesh of yours.
And destroy you
from the inside out,
just like I did this bitch.
But first,
I have a confession to make.
That's not Gabbie.
Gabbie!
Let me go!
Please,
just let her go.
You can have me,
you can have me.
I already have you.
Gabby!
I'll fucking kill you!
Stop!
You cruel fuck,
she's just a baby,
leave her alone!
Stop.
It's all your fault.
I told you that wasn't Gabbie.
See you soon.
Love you.
Jonathan!
No, no!
No!
You fucking bitch!
That's it!
Come on!
Kill me! Kill me!
No!
Everything you love is gone.
There is no hope,
there is no God.
Just let go!
So you can let me in!
Sienna!
Let her go!
Oh, you are strong,
aren't you?
Now I know why they chose you.
You really love that one,
don't you?
She's fighting for you,
Gabby.
You're all she's got left.
And you're the only thing
that's keeping her
from letting me in.
Gabby! No!
No!
Don't fucking touch her!
I'm sorry you didn't get
to open my present.
That's not fair.
Which one is yours, sweetie?
I said which one?
The one at the back
with the angels.
The angels, of course.
Did you wrap this yourself?
Shitty job.
Do you want to know
what Gabbie got you
for Christmas?
Yes.
Do you want to open it
yourself?
Yes.
So do it.
No!
Enough!
You said you wanted to open it.
Stop it, stop it!
Let her go!
Open it!
We're waiting.
Stop it!
Let her go!
Hope you like it.
Best gift ever.
Tell me how this tastes.
Oh, Gabs!
Oh, God.
How did you know?
I opened it.
I'm a snoop, remember?
Yeah.
Get down!
Gabbie!
Come on, fucker!
Mommy!
Mommy.
Mom!
Please!
Wake up!
Sienna!
Gabbie!
Sienna, I'm slipping!
Reach up, Gabbie!
Hold on!
Sienna,
I can't, I can't!
Grab on!
Sienna, I can't!
Yes you can, baby,
reach out!
Come on!
Grab it!
Come on, baby, work with me!
Come on.
Reach for it.
Hold, baby.
Pull up!
Sienna, I'm slipping!
Oh, God, help!
Sienna!
I love you.
Gabbie!
Gabbie.
I'll find you.
All is bright
Round yon virgin--
Oh, I'm sorry,
are you reading a book?
Just tell me
to shut up next time.
Oh, no.
It's okay.
This book is actually
a lot creepier
than I anticipated.
Horror?
Yeah.
I don't, uh...
I don't get
into all that blood and gore.
I'm more of a rom-com guy.
Frankenstein.
That's a good movie.
A classic.
You ok hun?
It's a Terrifier Christmas
Let the horror
fill your heart
Do you hear footsteps,
that's not Santa
It's a jolly clown named Art
He is a Miles County legend
With a smile that brings
on chill
On a journey
to outdo himself
Let's talk his latest kill
We saw your gleaming eyes
He'll kill the flesh right
off your bones
And shock with
a silent laugh
It's a Terrifier Christmas
Tum-ta-tum-ta-tum-ta-tum-ta